https://tjsbbank.co.in/privacy-policy

Preamble
“TJSB”, or “TJSB Sahakari Bank Ltd,” or “Bank” means “TJSB Sahakari Bank Ltd.” having its
Registered under the Multi State Co-operative Societies Act, 2002, under registration No.
MSCS/CR/287/2008 of 23/10/2008 and having its registered office at TJSB House, Plot No.B-
5, Road No.2, Wagle Industrial Estate, Thane (W)-400 604.
This Mobile Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applied to users of mobile banking through “TJSB Sahakari Bank Ltd.” The term “TJSB Sahakari Bank” or “TJSB Bank” or “we”, ”us” or “our” in any mobile banking application we own and control and in this Policy refers to TJSB Sahakari Bank Ltd. and our affiliates or subsidiaries. This Policy describes how the mobile banking application hereafter known as “Smart Money” or “TJSB Smart Money” or “Mobile Banking Application” to collect, use and share information from or about you and explains how the information may be shared or used.
Agreement to Policy
By viewing Mobile Banking Application or Smart Money of TJSB Sahakari Bank Ltd or by using TJSB Banks website “http://www.tjsbbank.co.in/” on a mobile device, you consent to
this policy which includes you consent to disclose and use information about you in the manner detailed in this policy. Other privacy policies may also apply in addition to the terms of this Mobile Privacy Policy, including but not limited to our Privacy Policy.
Information Collection, Use or Sharing
Information that we may collect about you through mobile banking includes information
that you voluntarily disclose at the time of subscription such as your name, primary a/c
number, alias a/c, secondary account number/s, mobile number and other contact
information; transaction information, information resulting from your mobile activity in
terms of your usage of the subscribed mobile banking service. We do not gather additional
information associated with your mobile device through cookies and other technologies. We
also do not share any of this information with any other company unless required to do so
by law or while handling any disputes that may arise.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or
promotional materials and other information.
Security
We apply several security measures to protect your information. Reply messages sent by the
Mobile Banking use masking features to hide the first few characters in your a/c numbers.
To help prevent misuse of services and authorize access to your banking information, you
are always required to type in your MPIN/TPIN provided by the bank or set by you from
time to time. As always, we strongly encourage you to assist us in that effort by not sharing
your MPIN with anyone. Though the security of your Personal Information is important to
us, there is no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is
100% secure. While we attempt to use commercially acceptable means to protect your
Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. The TJSB Sahakari Bank
Ltd. (Multi-State Scheduled Co-operative Bank) Mobile Banking Privacy Policy or method of
electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we attempt to use commercially acceptable means
to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of 04/02/2017 and will remain in effect except with respect
to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being
posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should
check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any
modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the
modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. We
are not responsible to separately/individually inform or intimate to registered customer for
change made in Privacy Policy by the bank.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will mention the same
prominently by notice on our authorised website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us on 1800223466 or
mobile@tjsb.co.in
Hyperlink Policy
Any hyper link to other Internet sites is at customer's own risk, the contents of which and the accuracy of opinions expressed are not verified, monitored or endorsed by TJSB Bank in any way or manner. TJSB Bank is not responsible for the setup of any hyperlink from a third party website to TJSB Bank's website. Any links so set up shall not constitute any form of co-operation with, or endorsement by, TJSB Bank of such third party website.
Disclaimer
The information & material content on this website is intended for general understanding of TJSB Bank and to help the public to get better exposure to information about the Bank and various products and services offered by the Bank.
Persons desiring to have additional information may contact Bank.
The information and material contained herein is subjected to change from time to time.
TJSB Bank is not liable for :
Any loss or damage arising out from the use of this data.
Any errors or omission in this information
Sitemap
TJSB BANK
HEAD OFFICE :
TJSB House, Plot No.5B,Road No.2,
Wagle Industrial Estate,
Best View in IE9 and Above.
)
Loan Tenure (months)
Interest Rate (%)
Calculate
Reset
Term Deposit Calculator ( Quarterly Cumulative )
Deposit Amount (
)
